

Applicant for:

iOS Developer (Swift) Upto 2000\$

Dr.JOY 25 April 2020

Bach Le

Main interests: iOS, Android

What skills, work projects or achievements make you a strong candidate for this position?

Note from ITviec: Bach Le skipped the cover letter.

Curriculum Vitae - Information Technology



Personal Details

Name	Lê Xuân Bách
Date of birth	02/06/1990
Address	40/105, Xuan La District, Ha Noi City
Phone Number	0934 402 234
Email	Bachlx26@gmail.com
Skype	Bachle26
Date available	02/2020
to start work	

Profile

I am a hardworking, highly programming skills with over 5 year experience for mobile (ios platform) development. Furthermore, I am conversant in a wide range of programming languages. I'm comfortable working either independent or a part of a team. So I am seeking a new opportunity that will allow me to expand on those skills.

Objective

- Working hard in order to accomplish my task.
- Become a team leader in next 5 years.
- Become a project manager in next 7 years.

Skills Summary

- Objective-C (SqLite, MapKit, Audio, Video, parse, social network, image...)
- Swift (> 3 years' experience)
- OS: Mac OS.
- Basic knowledge about Unity. C/C++, .Net.

Education

2010-2012: FPT - Aptech

Working Experience:

1. Qsoft Viet Nam, March 2012 – May 2013

Position: iOS Developer

- Code new modules with pre-agreed technical specifications
- Researched new technologies and put forward suitable solutions in order investigated and resolved issues relating to application functionally.
- Worked closely with client during implementation phases to ensure successful and timely outcome.
- Application maintenance
- 2. Appota, Naiscorp and freelancer, May 2013 February 2014

Position: iOS Developer (part time)

- Code new modules with pre-agreed technical specifications
- Researched new technologies and put forward suitable solutions in order investigated and resolved issues relating to application functionally.
- Developing game/product of company base on game system such as ibet88, vuachip
- 3. Fruitful Tech February 2014

Position: iOS Developer

- Support technical with members.
- Code new modules with pre-agreed technical specifications
- Researched new technologies and put forward suitable solutions in order investigated and resolved issues relating to application functionally.

- Worked closely with client during implementation phases to ensure successful and timely outcome.
- Application maintenance

4. VNTRIP June 2015 – January 2017

Position: iOS Developer

- Support technical with members.
- Code new modules with pre-agreed technical specifications
- Researched new technologies and put forward suitable solutions in order investigated and resolved issues relating to application functionally.
- Worked closely with client during implementation phases to ensure successful and timely outcome.
- Application maintenance

5. Tripi January 2017 – June 2019

Position: iOS Developer

- Support technical with members.
- Code new modules with pre-agreed technical specifications
- Researched new technologies and put forward suitable solutions in order investigated and resolved issues relating to application functionally.
- Worked closely with client during implementation phases to ensure successful and timely outcome.
- Application maintenance

6. Freelancer June 2019

Projects:

Project's name: Silver Top Taxi, Geelong Taxi Network, West Suburban

Link App:

https://itunes.apple.com/au/app/silver-top-taxi/id552851170?mt=8

 $\underline{https://itunes.apple.com/au/app/west-suburban/id565061765?mt{=}8}$

https://itunes.apple.com/au/app/geelong-taxi-network/id472838648?mt=8

Project size(Number of people):4 Turong tự ứng dụng Uber Taxi mở

rộng them một số chức năng

Role: Main developer

Project's name: Lịch Như Ý

Link App:

https://itunes.apple.com/vn/app/lich-nhu-y/id797395252?mt=8

Project size(Number of people):1 Lịch vạn niên ngoài các tính năng

lịch cơ bản như xem giờ hoàng đạo,can chi, ngày giờ tốt xấu,hướng xuất hành, việc nên và không nên làm trong ngày thì bạn còn có thể xem

lịch theo Cung hoàng đạo.

Project's name: vntrip.vn

Role: Main developer

Link App:

 $\underline{https://itunes.apple.com/vn/app/vntrip-at-phong-khach-}$

san/id1046183734?l=vi&mt=8

Project size(Number of people): 2	Ứng dụng đặt phòng khách sạn
Role: Main developer	

Project's name: Tripi Parner, Dinogo				
Link App:				
https://apps.apple.com/vn/app/tripi-partner-b2b	o-travel-deals/id1356994818			
$\frac{https://apps.apple.com/us/app/dinogo-du-1\%E1\%BB\%8Bch-kh\%C3\%B4ng-lo-\%C3\%A2u/id1459487385}$				
Project size(Number of people) : 2	Ứng dụng đặt vé máy bay			
Role: Main developer				

Other project for iOs platform: Kid's Travel Journal, Barni, Phong tục cổ truyền - Văn khấn, Kid's Travel Journal

Hobbies: Movies, Techniques, Football.